CHRISTIAN MILICEVIC

DEVELOPER & CYBERSEC

CURRICULUM VITAE

PROFILE



I am a recent IT graduate of the Queensland University of Technology who is commencing a career in software development, programming and cyber security. I supported my university studies with casual employment, focusing on IT, warehousing and mechanics. I have a strong worth ethic and enjoy team-based projects, meeting with people from diverse backgrounds and experiences, and I thrive on challenges that involve multiple responsibilities.

EXPERIENCE

KJR/DATARWE

Junior Consultant (DevSecOps) – permanent full-time | Brisbane QLD | May 2022 – Sep 2022

KJR is a consulting company that been around for 25 years. They're main focus is on Software Quality & Aussrance, but offers a range of services for clients such as Software development, QA, DevSecOps and Data Quality & Al Assurance. Datarwe is KJR sister company that has been around for three years that is a clinical Data-as-a-Service provider for the public and private healthcare sector. My main responsibilities in this role while being at KJR and Datarwe are:

- Managing least privilege access with AWS IAM JSON security polices for whole AWS Cloud Infrastructure.
- Fixing any permissions issues with Git/AWS for other developers
- Scripting in Python AWS CDK to automate cloud architecture in Visual Studio with Ubuntu/WSL Linux and Git terminl/CodeCommit
- Spinning up AWS infrastructure such as: EC2, CLI, SageMaker, Athena/SQL, S3, CodeCommit, Lambda, IAM, CloudFormation, VPC, Lake formation, Workspaces, Directory Service, CloudTrail, CloudShell, Secret Managers
- Bug fixing and code clean up;

SUNCORP

Software Engineer Cybersecurity/DevSecOps – permanent full-time | Brisbane QLD | Nov 2021 – March 2022

Suncorp is an Australian based finance and banking company, that is one of Australia's biggest. It is based in Brisbane Queensland and was once owned by the Queensland Government. They recently built a new office building in Queen Street to combine the whole team into one office building. My responsibilities in this role include:

- Bug fixing and code clean up;
- Automating system platforms for teams to use;
- Solving system platform problems;
- Solving system platform problems;
- Improving, integrating matain and securing and platform features;
- On call roster basis;

CONTACT



Camira, Brisbane, Australia

(PO Box 270 INDOOROOPILLY CENTRE QLD 4068)



0481 335 145



cmilicevic3@gmail.com



www.christianmilicevic.com (Portfolio)

EDUCATION

AWS CERTIFIED CLOUD PRACTITIONER

Amazon Web Service, 2022

GRADUATE CERTIFICATE IN CYBERSECURITY & NETWORKING

Melbourne Institute of Technology, 2021

BACHELOR OF GAMES & INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENTS (SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES)

Queensland University of Technology, 2020

DIPLOMA OF DIGITAL INTERACTIVE GAME DESIGN

Queensland TAFE – Southbank campus, 2017

QUEENSLAND CERTIFICATE OF EDUCATION

John Paul College, Daisy Hill QLD, 2016

ACHIEVEMENTS

SPONSORED STUDY

In 2021, I was awarded a Commonwealth Government grant to undertake postgraduate studies in cyber security through MIT.

ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT

I was awarded a Bachelor with Distinction upon completion of my studies in IT at QUT in 2020.

CHRISTIAN MILICEVIC

DEVELOPER & CYBERSEC

CURRICULUM VITAE

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

GAMELOFT

Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer – permanent full-time | Brisbane QLD | Jun 2021 – Nov 2021

Gameloft is a global publisher of digital and social games for mobile phones. With headquarters in France, it has a presence and partnership network in 148 countries. All games are developed inhouse and the company has the largest development and creation team in the digital games industry. My responsibilities in this role include:

- · Querying Cloud database using SQL, Snowflake and documenting working solutions;
- Querying and graphing Snowflake queries into Looker API;
- · CI/CD pipeline Jenkins;
- · Reporting, reviewing and documenting bugs in Jira;
- Project-based game delivery, including current project, The Oregon Trail Game;
- Utilising iPhone, Mac OS, Apple TV systems as part of project delivery; and
- · Participating in team-based meetings and discussions.

FILEMAN

Graduate Solutions Programmer / Support Engineer (Junior Developer) — Permanent Full-Time | Paradise Point QLD | Feb 2021 — Jun 2021

Fileman is an Australian-based business that develops and maintains a Cloud-based management tool to enable legal corporations to manage the storage and destruction of closed case files. It enables instant location, retrieval and addition to case documents. My main duties int his position included:

- Programming, source control and code quality control;
- Implementing new systems and features;
- Bug fixing and code clean up;
- Handling tickets from clients (legal professionals); and
- Communicating with other team members and clients.

PREVIOUS CASUAL POSITIONS

Coles Group LTD (Warehouse Division) – Part-time Casual | Forest Lake QLD | 2018-2021

Goals A+N – IT Relocation Technician – Casual | Geebung QLD | 2018 – 2018

Stadiums QLD – Events Staff – Part-time Casual | Woolloongabba QLD | 2017 – 2020

City Beach Warehouse – Picker/Packer – Part-time Casual | Murrarie QLD | 2017 – 2018

N&D Mechanical Repairs – Mechanic's Assistant – Part-time Casual | Wacol QLD | 2015 – 2017

PERSONAL DATA

CITIZENSHIP

Australian (by birth)

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

- Car enthusiast
- IT enthusiast
- Health & fitness
- International travel
- Snowboarding
- Scuba diving

IT PROGRAMS & LANGUAGES

- AWS (EC2, CLI, CDK, CodeCommit, Lambda, IAM, CloudFormatiuon, VPC, Lake formation, Workspaces, Directory Service, CloudTrail, CloudShell, Secrets Managers)
- · Jenkins
- Python (AWS CDK, Boto3)
- HTML, CSS, JS
- SQL Server, MySQL
- JFrog Xray, JFrog Artifactory
- C# (.NET, ASP.NET, Window Forms)
- Git, GitHub Desktop, Git Bash
- · Jira, Confluence, Bitbucket
- Keepass
- · Atom, Visual Studios, Visual Studio Code
- Unity
- Splunk, Fortify
- Snowflake, Looker
- Ubuntu Linux

REFERENCES

GAMELOFT

Mrs M Ingham Former supervisor Contact details upon request

KJR

Mr O Sellwood Software Engineer Contact details upon request